BOY SUGIJAKKO

sugijakkoboy@gmail.com | boysugi20.github.io

ABOUT ME

A dedicated, hardworking, responsible, and loyal individual with 2+ years of experience working, developing, and maintaining web applications as a system analyst in a renowned world class university. Interested in learning new things and eager to share what they've learned with others. Capable of excelling both individually and as a member of a team.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2022 - PRESENT

SENIOR SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Manage project timeline
- Design applications that are efficient to improve user experience and reduce system load
- Provide documentation (Data Flow Diagram, Entity Relationship Diagram, and Deployment Documents)

OCT 2021 - OCT 2022

SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Debug, fix, or enhance Stored Procedures used in application to fetch data from database
- Analyze requirements based on user needs
- Collaborate with programmers to develop new features
- Collaborate with programmers to enhance application to fit new user needs
- Trace errors caused by incorrect data on database

MAR 2020 - OCT 2021

JUNIOR SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Collaborate with programmers to debug applications
- Assist seniors on solving application errors
- Assist users with problems on application usage

EDUCATION

JUN 2022 – PRESENT

MA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY (3.9 GPA)

Thesis title: "Lightweight Face Recognition-Based Portable Attendance System With Liveness Detection"

SEP 2018 – JUN 2022

BA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY (3.74 GPA)

Thesis title: "Masked Face Recognition for a Lightweight School Attendance Management System during COVID-19 Pandemic"

SKILLS

- SQL
- Python
- Database
- Information Technology

- System Testing
- System Analysis
- Analytical Skills
- Internet of Things